Guide to the Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated RL.11128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 2002-2012 and undated; 12
  - Originals, 2002-2012 and undated; 99
    - March of Dimes Premature Birth PSAs, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-079)
    - Cartoon Network Animate Your World PSA, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-080)
    - Habitat for Humanity--MLB national, 2005 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-081)
    - Habitat for Humanity--MLB final reel all spots, 2005 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-082)
    - Kellogg's/Komen Keep the Promise, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-083)
    - Target/Salvation Army Songs for a Cause, 2008 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-001)
    - Alliance to Save Energy PSAs, undated (Box AV2, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-002)
    - Alliance to Save Energy PSAs (Spanish), undated (Box AV2, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-003)
    - Drive Smarter Challenge ringtone (Spanish), undated (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-004)
    - Jane Arden, Saved, 2004 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-005)
    - American Idol, What the World Needs Now is Love, 2003 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-006)
    - American Idol, God Bless the USA, 2003 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-007)
    - Elefanten Steps to Art, Bumblebees and Googleheads, fun songs by Laurie Berkner, 2002 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-008)
    - Target/Salvation Army Songs for Greater Good, 2007 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-009)
    - Boost Mobile Rock Corps mixtape, 2006 (Box AV11, Audio-cd RL11030-CD-010)
    - Huddle to Fight Hunger highlights video, cinema spot (flash drive), 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-001)
    - Jiffy Lube Maintenance Partners for Life (flash drive), 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-002)
    - United Nations Foundation Girl Up: Recap; In the Know; Kites in the Wind, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-003)
    - Walton Isaacson Bellies PSA (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-004)
    - Touchdown for Tots PSAs (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-005)
    - Connect a Million Minds (flash drive_, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-006)
    - Get Schooled (flash drive), 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-007)
    - National Association of Realtors Houselogic (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-008)
    - Pearson Foundation We Give Books (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-009)
    - Have You Heard (flash drive), 2009 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-010)
    - Disney Oceans videos (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-011)
    - Cheesecake Factory Drive Out Hunger (flash drive), 2009 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-012)
    - Box Tops for Education, Power of One (flash drive), 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-013)
    - Read and Rise supporting audio and video (Flash drive), 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-014)
    - Teens for Jeans (flash drive in Taz), 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-015)
    - Kohl's Women's Health/Breast Cancer Initiative (flash drive), 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-016)
    - Nature Valley National Parks Project (flash drive), 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-017)
    - General Mills I 3 BKFST (flash drive), 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-018)
    - Scholastic Word Girl, Be Big, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-019)
    - Soccket, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-020)
    - Walmart Snow, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-021)
    - We Give Books, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-022)
    - P&G Special Olympics Final, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-023)
    - Reality Check, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-024)
    - Kohl's Love to Give, Happy to Save broadcast coverage, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-025)
    - Kohl's Every Ribbon Tells a Story, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-026)
    - Hanes Virtual Sock Drive, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-027)
    - CVS Caremark Walk With Me, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-028)
    - Children's Cancer Association and Papa Murphy's Radiothon clips, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-029)
    - Walton Isaacson Bellies PSA (flash drive), 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-030)
    - Delta Sky Miles, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-031)
    - Fuel Your School, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-032)
    - Walton Isaacson Bellies PSA (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-033)
    - Champions presented by Walmart and Sam's Club, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-034)
    - Vemma NEXT commercials, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-035)
    - General Mills I 3 BKFST (flash drive), 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-036)
    - Do Something 101 School Supply Drive, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-037)
    - New Balance Komen partnership, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-038)
    - SunChips videos, 2009 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-039)
    - Produce for Kids YouTube, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-040)
    - Aflac Friends of a Feather, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-041)
    - Omega Project Orbis documentary, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-042)
    - Rotary This Close creative, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-043)
    - TakePart Contagion Master, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-044)
    - Kohl's Susan G. Komen Southeast Wisconsin Race for the Cure, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-045)
    - Yoplait Fox Denver Pink House, 2012 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-046)
    - Yahoo! You In?, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-047)
    - Chivas Regal Espiritu de Progreso Latino, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-048)
    - End Malaria, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-049)
    - Kohl's Race for the Cure, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-050)
    - St. Jude Children Hospital PlayNetwork, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-051)
    - End Malaria, 2011 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-052)
    - CYBEX Pink Ribbon Run sample broadcast news, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-053)
    - End Malaria, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-054)
    - Mens WearHouse Attack the Mancession National Suit Drive sizzle media, 2010 (Box AV12, Disk RL11030-FD-055)
    - VH1 Save the Music Foundation Electronic Press Kit, 2005 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-Beta-001)